in this lecture we'll speak about social
在本讲座中，我们将谈论社交
choice functions the most famous
选择功能最著名
impossibility results pertain to social
不可能结果与社会有关
welfare function and in particular the
福利功能，尤其是
arrows impossibility theorem is widely
箭头不可能定理广泛
known and we have discussed that before
已知，我们之前已经讨论过
now it might be thought that the problem
现在可能会认为问题出在
lies in the fact that social welfare
在于社会福利
functions require you to specify as an
函数需要您指定为
output of the process and entire
过程和整个过程的输出
ordering and that might be highly
订购，这可能是高度
constraining but if you only need it to
约束，但是如果您只需要它
pick a winner as does a social choice
选择优胜者，社会选择也一样
function then you would escape these
功能，那么您将逃脱这些
paradoxes it turns out that the answer
矛盾的是，答案
is no but first we need to sort of
不是，但是首先我们需要
redefine our criteria a little bit
重新定义我们的标准
because the notions of Pareto efficiency
因为帕累托效率的概念
and independence of irrelevant
与无关无关
alternatives just aren't well-defined in
替代品的定义不明确
the context of a social choice function
社会选择功能的背景
but we will see that there are closely
但我们会发现
related notions that are well defined so
定义明确的相关概念
let's first define weak Pareto
首先定义弱帕累托
efficiency
效率
and we'll say that a software choice
我们会说软件选择
function C is weakly Pareto efficient if
函数C弱于帕累托效率
essentially it never elects a dominated
从根本上说，它从不选举一个被统治者
outcome or candidate so if there is a a
结果或候选人，如果有的话
candidate o - such that there is some
候选o-这样有一些
other candidate or one that is always
其他候选人或永远是
preferred to Oh - by every by every
喜欢哦-每个人一个
voter then the weaker candidate Oh -
选民再弱者候选人哦-
would never be elected seems like a
永远不会当选似乎
reasonable criterion and we'll call that
合理的标准，我们称之为
weak Pareto efficiency in place of
帕累托效率低下
independent of irrelevant alternative
独立于无关的选择
the alternative will have the notion of
替代方案将具有
monotonicity and informally as I written
单调性和我写的非正式
here at the at the bottom it says that
在底部的底部说
if you have a winner if we increase the
如果您有赢家，如果我们增加
support
支持
for that candidate they would still
对于那个候选人，他们仍然会
remain a winner so formally speaking
如此正式地保持赢家
will say that the subject response is
会说主题回应是
monotonic if we if we take any candidate
如果我们接受任何候选人，则单调
oh and an infestation for any preference
哦，还有什么偏爱
profile
轮廓
this one over here if under this
如果在这个下面
preference profile always selected then
然后总是选择首选项配置文件
if we look at any other preference
如果我们看看其他任何偏好
profile if it has the property that for
配置文件，如果它具有
every agent and every other outcome Oh
每一个特工和每一个其他的结果哦
prime if under the original preference
如果在原始偏好下为素数
Oh was preferred to O prime which is
哦比O素好
also under the new preference so one the
在新的偏好下，所以一个
that original winner Oh never lost
原来的赢家哦，永不丢失
support maybe only gained support then
支持可能只是获得支持
under those condition it better be the
在这种情况下，最好是
case that on the new preference order in
在新的优先顺序上的情况
which Oh only got more support it would
哦，只会得到更多的支持
still be the so for choice the winner
仍然是获胜者的选择
again a reasonable property to require
再次需要合理的财产
the last notion of dictatorship are
独裁的最后一个概念是
similar to what you see in social
类似于您在社交中看到的
welfare simply says that C is
福利只是说C是
dictatorial if there's some agents whose
是否有一些代理人
top choice is always the social choice
最高的选择永远是社会的选择
this is the bad news
这是个坏消息
the molar status weight theorem tells us
摩尔状态权重定理告诉我们
that we can't have all three so if a
我们不能同时拥有这三个，所以如果一个
social choice function is Pareto
社会选择功能是帕累托
efficient and monotonic it must be
高效且单调的
dictatorial and so after all social
独裁的，所以毕竟是社会的
choice functions aren't more benign the
选择功能不是更好
social welfare function and we won't go
社会福利功能，我们不会去
through the proof but the intuition is
通过证明，但直觉是
that in order to determine the relative
为了确定相对
ordering among candidates we need to
我们需要在候选人中排序
sort of probe it everywhere and
到处都有探测
and if we probe it enough we'll get the
如果我们对其进行足够的研究，我们将获得
entire social social welfare function
整个社会的社会福利职能
and since the since the function social
自从功能社会以来
choice function must be defined for all
必须为所有定义选择功能
inputs as we vary the inputs we can find
输入，因为我们改变了我们可以找到的输入
the total software for ordering so in
订购总软件
fact or we can use a social choice
事实，或者我们可以使用社会选择
function to recover the social welfare
恢复社会福利的功能
fact that the intuition behind the proof
事实上，证明背后的直觉
and why social drug functions are as may
以及为什么社会毒品功能如此
be counterintuitive or complicated and
违反直觉或复杂
social welfare functions now just two
社会福利职能现在只有两个
tests on tuition again let's consider an
再次进行学费测试让我们考虑
example and let's take for allottee
例子，让我们来分配
which perhaps on the face of it might
也许从表面上看
contradict the malar shadows weight
与黄斑阴影的重量矛盾
theorem clearly poor allottee is Pareto
定理显然是可怜的分配者是帕累托
efficient in other words if everybody
换句话说，如果每个人都有效
prefers some candidate to a another
偏爱某个候选人
candidate that other weaker candidate
那个其他较弱的候选人
will never be the choice and it's
永远不会是选择，这是
founded dictatorial obviously so the
成立专政显然是这样
theorem says it cannot be monotonic
定理说它不能单调
intuitive you might think it is
直观的你可能会认为是
monotonic but here's a counter example
单调的，但这是一个反例
so here are these seven agents and there
所以这是这七个特工
are three preference profiles the three
是三个偏好配置文件，三个
of the agent prefer A to B to C etc and
的代理商更喜欢A而不是B而不是C等，并且
clearly then a would be the winner under
显然，那么a将是下一个赢家
poor ality because three agents would
差劲，因为三个特工会
vote for a now what happens if we go and
现在投票，如果我们去
we modify this we modify this preference
我们修改此，我们修改此首选项
to this preference we simply make a
为此，我们只需
situation bitter C was preferred to a
情况C比C偏爱
originally and now a is preferred to C
最初，现在A优于C
and all other preferences
和所有其他偏好
to a remain the same so clear surely you
保持不变，所以请确保您清楚
would say a as is doing as well as it
会说做得很好
would have done originally and
本来可以做到的，
monotonicity would say that your
单调性表示您
children the winner but clearly in this
孩子赢家，但显然
case they're not four agents were voting
如果他们不是四个特工在投票
for B versus only three for a so B would
对于B来说，只有三个
be the winner now so plurality is not
现在成为赢家，所以不是多元化
monotonic
单调的